### Imaduddin Abdul Karim

#### Multi-platform Mobile Application Developer

An 8-semester Telecommunication Engineering student from Telkom University with a wide interest and passion for technology and programming who enjoys taking on new projects and facing new challenges. Previous experience in laboratory organizations has given me good time management, leadership and communication skills. I love learning new things, especially in the areas of mobile development, artificial intelligence and data science. In addition, I have experience in the field of graphic design.



Bandung, West Java, Indonesia





# **Work Experience**

## Creative Manager and Research Assistant • IMV Laboratory

Working as a research assistant and creative content manager.

January 2022 - Present

#### Creative Manager • Basic Computing Laboratory | Telkom University

Creative Content Manager and teaches practicum on algorithms and programming in electrical, physics, biomedical and telecommunications engineering.

July 2021 - Aug 2022

#### Practicum Assistant • Basic Computing Laboratory | Telkom University

Teaches practicum on algorithms and programming in electrical, physics, biomedical and telecommunications engineering.

May 2020 - Aug 2022

#### Education



2019 - 2023

#### **Universitas Telkom**

**Bachelor of Engineering-BE** 

#### Skills

- Telecommunications Engineering
- Front-End Development
- Machine Learning
- Flutter App Development
- · Data Analytics

# Languages

- English Intermediate
- Indonesian Professional

- Graphic Design
- UI/UX Designer

# Certification

• TensorFlow Developer Certificate